[
  {
    "question": "Who holds the record for the most submission victories in UFC history?",
    "options": [
      "Demian Maia",
      "Royce Gracie",
      "Khabib Nurmagomedov",
      "Frank Mir"
    ],
    "answer": "Demian Maia"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which UFC fighter is known for his 'Stockton Slap'?",
    "options": [
      "Nick Diaz",
      "Nate Diaz",
      "Donald Cerrone",
      "Tony Ferguson"
    ],
    "answer": "Nick Diaz"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the first female fighter to win UFC championships in two different weight classes?",
    "options": [
      "Valentina Shevchenko",
      "Amanda Nunes",
      "Ronda Rousey",
      "Cris Cyborg"
    ],
    "answer": "Amanda Nunes"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the nickname of fighter Donald Cerrone?",
    "options": [
      "Cowboy",
      "The Notorious",
      "The Eagle",
      "The Pitbull"
    ],
    "answer": "Cowboy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which UFC fighter is known for his 'freakshow' persona and unique fighting style?",
    "options": [
      "Conor McGregor",
      "Jon Jones",
      "Anderson Silva",
      "Tony Ferguson"
    ],
    "answer": "Tony Ferguson"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who holds the record for the fastest submission in a UFC title fight?",
    "options": [
      "Ronda Rousey",
      "Demetrious Johnson",
      "Georges St-Pierre",
      "B.J. Penn"
    ],
    "answer": "Ronda Rousey"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which fighter famously knocked out Alistair Overeem with a stunning left hook at UFC 218?",
    "options": [
      "Stipe Miocic",
      "Francis Ngannou",
      "Derrick Lewis",
      "Junior dos Santos"
    ],
    "answer": "Francis Ngannou"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is known as 'The Beast' in the UFC?",
    "options": [
      "Francis Ngannou",
      "Brock Lesnar",
      "Cain Velasquez",
      "Derrick Lewis"
    ],
    "answer": "Brock Lesnar"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the UFC reality television series where fighters compete for a UFC contract?",
    "options": [
      "The Ultimate Fighter",
      "Fight Night",
      "UFC Primetime",
      "Dana White's Contender Series"
    ],
    "answer": "The Ultimate Fighter"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which UFC fighter is known for his signature spinning wheel kick knockout against Terry Etim at UFC 142?",
    "options": [
      "Anthony Pettis",
      "Edson Barboza",
      "Thiago Santos",
      "Uriah Hall"
    ],
    "answer": "Edson Barboza"
  }
]